Aaron Ziegelman Foundation collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 4: Moving images
  - Interview with Clara Pozner, AFC 2003/002: MV001; Tape 1 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with Clara Pozner, AFC 2003/002: MV002; Tape 2 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with Clara Pozner, AFC 2003/002: MV003; Tape 3 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with Clara Pozner, AFC 2003/002: MV004; Tape 4 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with Clara Pozner, AFC 2003/002: MV005; Tape 5 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with Clara Pozner, AFC 2003/002: MV006; Tape 6 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with Clara Pozner, AFC 2003/002: MV007; Tape 7 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview: Yosef Karpus by Rishon Lezion T.A., 1995-07-08, AFC 2003/002: MV008; Tape 1 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview: Yosef Karpus by Rishon Lezion, T.A., 1995-07-08, AFC 2003/002: MV009; Tape 2 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview: Yosef Karpus by Amy Avital, 1995-07-08, AFC 2003/002: MV010; Tape 3 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview: Yosef Karpus by Amy Avital, 1995-07-08, AFC 2003/002: MV011; Tape 4 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview: Yosef Karpus by Amy Avital, 1995-07-08, AFC 2003/002: MV012; Tape 5 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview: Yosef Karpus by Amy Avital, 1995-07-08, AFC 2003/002: MV013; Tape 6 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview: Yosef Karpus by Amy Avital, 1995-07-08, AFC 2003/002: MV014; Tape 7 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview: Yosef Karpus by Amy Avital, 1995-07-08, AFC 2003/002: MV015; Tape 8 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Luboml Documentary Project, 2002-01-09, AFC 2003/002: MV016; Tape 1 of 1, Betacam SP, 31:00 minutes
  - Luboml Documentary Project, 2002-01-09, AFC 2003/002: MV017; Tape 1 of 2, Betacam SP, 27:30 minutes
  - Luboml Documentary Project, 2002-01-09, AFC 2003/002: MV018; Tape 2 of 1, Betacam SP, 31:00 minutes
  - Luboml Documentary Project, 2002-01-09, AFC 2003/002: MV019; Tape 2 of 2, Betacam SP, 31:00 minutes
  - Luboml Documentary Project, 2002-01-09, AFC 2003/002: MV020; Tape 3, Betacam SP, 14:25 minutes
  - Luboml Documentary Project, 2002-01-09, AFC 2003/002: MV021; Tape 4, Betacam SP, 31:00 minutes
  - Luboml Documentary Project, 2002-01-09, AFC 2003/002: MV022; Tape 1-3 Chip Pt 1, Betacam SP, 31:00 minutes
  - Luboml Documentary Project, 2002-01-09, AFC 2003/002: MV023; Tape 1-3 Chip Pt 2, Betacam SP, 31:30 minutes
  - Luboml Documentary Project, 2002-01-09, AFC 2003/002: MV024; Tape 2-3 Chip Pt. 1, Betacam SP, 31:30 minutes
  - Luboml Documentary Project, 2002-01-09, AFC 2003/002: MV025; Tape 2-3 Chip Pt. 2, Betacam SP, 13:15 minutes
  - Luboml Documentary Project, 2002-01-09, AFC 2003/002: MV026; From DV Cam, 14:45 minutes
  - Interview With: Anne Friedman Gershengorn, 1995-06-19, AFC 2003/002: MV027; Tape 1 of 3, Betacam SP
  - Interview With: Anne Friedman Gershengorn, 1995-06-19, AFC 2003/002: MV028; Tape 2 of 3, Betacam SP
  - Interview With: Anne Friedman Gershengorn, 1995-06-19, AFC 2003/002: MV029; Tape 3 of 3, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Nathan Eiger, 1995-07-17, AFC 2003/002: MV030; Tape 1 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Nathan Eiger, 1995-07-17, AFC 2003/002: MV031; Tape 2 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Nathan Eiger, 1995-07-17, AFC 2003/002: MV032; Tape 3 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Nathan Eiger, 1995-07-19, AFC 2003/002: MV033; Tape 4 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Nathan Eiger, 1995-07-19, AFC 2003/002: MV034; Tape 5 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Nathan Eiger, 1995-07-19, AFC 2003/002: MV035; Tape 6 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Victor Lichtmacher, 1995-07-06, AFC 2003/002: MV036; Tape 1 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Victor Lichtmacher, 1995-07-06, AFC 2003/002: MV037; Tape 2 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Victor Lichtmacher, 1995-07-06, AFC 2003/002: MV038; Tape 3 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Victor Lichtmacher, 1995-07-06, AFC 2003/002: MV039; Tape 4 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Victor Lichtmacher, 1995-07-06, AFC 2003/002: MV040; Tape 5 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Victor Lichtmacher, 1995-07-06, AFC 2003/002: MV041; Tape 6 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Victor Lichtmacher, 1995-07-06, AFC 2003/002: MV042; Tape 7 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Nathan Sobel, 1995-07-11, AFC 2003/002: MV043; Tape 1 of 9, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Nathan Sobel, 1995-07-11, AFC 2003/002: MV044; Tape 2 of 9, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Nathan Sobel, 1995-07-11, AFC 2003/002: MV045; Tape 3 of 9, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Nathan Sobel, 1995-07-11, AFC 2003/002: MV046; Tape 4 of 9, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Nathan Sobel, 1995-07-11, AFC 2003/002: MV047; Tape 5 of 9, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Nathan Sobel, 1995-07-11, AFC 2003/002: MV048; Tape 6 of 9, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Nathan Sobel, 1995-07-11, AFC 2003/002: MV049; Tape 7 of 9, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Nathan Sobel, 1995-07-11, AFC 2003/002: MV050; Tape 8 of 9, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Nathan Sobel, 1995-07-11, AFC 2003/002: MV051; Tape 9 of 9, Betacam SP
  - Sonia Orbuch interviewed by Sandra Bendayan, 1994-12-06, AFC 2003/002: MV052; Tape 1 of 2, Betacam SP, 4 hours
  - Sonja Orbuch, 1995-01-05, AFC 2003/002: MV053; Tape 2 of 2, Betacam SP, 3 hours
  - Interview with: Aaron Ziegelman, 1995-07-25, AFC 2003/002: MV054; Tape 1 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Aaron Ziegelman, 1995-07-25, AFC 2003/002: MV055; Tape 2 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Aaron Ziegelman, 1995-07-25, AFC 2003/002: MV056; Tape 3 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Aaron Ziegelman, 1995-07-25, AFC 2003/002: MV057; Tape 4 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Aaron Ziegelman, 1995-07-25, AFC 2003/002: MV058; Tape 5 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Aaron Ziegelman, 1995-07-25, AFC 2003/002: MV059; Tape 6 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Lillian Chanales, 1995-07-25, AFC 2003/002: MV060; Tape 1 of 3, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Lillian Chanales, 1995-07-25, AFC 2003/002: MV061; Tape 2 of 3, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Lillian Chanales, 1995-07-25, AFC 2003/002: MV062; Tape 3 of 3, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Bernie Meller, 1995-09-21, AFC 2003/002: MV063; Tape 1 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Bernie Meller, 1995-09-21, AFC 2003/002: MV064; Tape 2 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Bernie Meller, 1995-09-21, AFC 2003/002: MV065; Tape 3 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Bernie Meller, 1995-09-21, AFC 2003/002: MV066; Tape 4 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Bernie Meller, 1995-09-21, AFC 2003/002: MV067; Tape 5 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Bernie Meller, 1995-09-21, AFC 2003/002: MV068; Tape 6 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Bernie Meller, 1995-09-21, AFC 2003/002: MV069; Tape 7 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Bernie Meller, 1995-09-21, AFC 2003/002: MV070; Tape 8 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Victor Gershengorn, 1995-06-19, AFC 2003/002: MV071; Tape 1 of 5, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Victor Gershengorn, 1995-06-19, AFC 2003/002: MV072; Tape 2 of 5, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Victor Gershengorn, 1995-06-19, AFC 2003/002: MV073; Tape 3 of 5, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Victor Gershengorn, 1995-06-19, AFC 2003/002: MV074; Tape 4 of 5, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Victor Gershengorn, 1995-06-19, AFC 2003/002: MV075; Tape 5 of 5, Betacam SP
  - Moshe Shalev, 1995-06-30, AFC 2003/002: MV076; Tape 1 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Moshe Shalev, 1995-06-30, AFC 2003/002: MV077; Tape 2 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Moshe Shalev, 1995-06-30, AFC 2003/002: MV078; Tape 3 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Moshe Shalev, 1995-06-30, AFC 2003/002: MV079; Tape 4 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Moshe Shalev, 1995-06-30, AFC 2003/002: MV080; Tape 5 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Moshe Shalev, 1995-06-30, AFC 2003/002: MV081; Tape 6 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: May Goodman, 1995-08-13, AFC 2003/002: MV082; Tape 1 of 5, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: May Goodman, 1995-08-13, AFC 2003/002: MV083; Tape 2 of 5, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: May Goodman, 1995-08-13, AFC 2003/002: MV084; Tape 3 of 5, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: May Goodman, 1995-08-13, AFC 2003/002: MV085; Tape 4 of 5, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: May Goodman, 1995-08-13, AFC 2003/002: MV086; Tape 5 of 5, Betacam SP
  - Riwa Plotnik, 1996-08-01, AFC 2003/002: MV087; Tape 1 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Riwa Plotnik, 1996-08-01, AFC 2003/002: MV088; Tape 2 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Riwa Plotnik, 1996-08-01, AFC 2003/002: MV089; Tape 3 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Riwa Plotnik, 1996-08-01, AFC 2003/002: MV090; Tape 4 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Riwa Plotnik, 1996-08-01, AFC 2003/002: MV091; Tape 5 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Riwa Plotnik, 1996-08-01, AFC 2003/002: MV092; Tape 6 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Riwa Plotnik, 1996-08-01, AFC 2003/002: MV093; Tape 7 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Abe Getman, 1995-07-18, AFC 2003/002: MV094; Tape 1 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Abe Getman, 1995-07-18, AFC 2003/002: MV095; Tape 2 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Abe Getman, 1995-07-18, AFC 2003/002: MV096; Tape 3 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Abe Getman, 1995-07-18, AFC 2003/002: MV097; Tape 4 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Abe Getman, 1995-07-18, AFC 2003/002: MV098; Tape 5 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Abe Getman, 1995-07-18, AFC 2003/002: MV099; Tape 6 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Abe Getman, 1995-07-18, AFC 2003/002: MV100; Tape 7 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Abe Getman, 1995-07-18, AFC 2003/002: MV101; Tape 8 of 8, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Esther Kessler, 1995-05-24, AFC 2003/002: MV102; Roll 1
  - Interview with: Esther Kessler, 1995-05-24, AFC 2003/002: MV103; Roll 2
  - Interview with: Esther Kessler, 1995-05-24, AFC 2003/002: MV104; Roll 3
  - Interview with: Esther Kessler, 1995-05-24, AFC 2003/002: MV105; Roll 4
  - Interview with: Esther Kessler, 1995-05-24, AFC 2003/002: MV106; Roll 5
  - Interview with: Esther Kessler, 1995-05-24, AFC 2003/002: MV107; Roll 6
  - Interview with: Esther Pachter, 1995-08-15, AFC 2003/002: MV108; Tape 1 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Esther Pachter, 1995-08-15, AFC 2003/002: MV109; Tape 2 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Esther Pachter, 1995-08-15, AFC 2003/002: MV110; Tape 3 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Esther Pachter, 1995-08-15, AFC 2003/002: MV111; Tape 4 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Esther Pachter, 1995-08-15, AFC 2003/002: MV112; Tape 5 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Esther Pachter, 1995-08-15, AFC 2003/002: MV113; Tape 6 of 6, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Benjamin Rosenzweig, 1995-07-10, AFC 2003/002: MV114; Tape 1 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Benjamin Rosenzweig, 1995-07-10, AFC 2003/002: MV115; Tape 2 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Benjamin Rosenzweig, 1995-07-10, AFC 2003/002: MV116; Tape 3 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Benjamin Rosenzweig, 1995-07-10, AFC 2003/002: MV117; Tape 4 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Benjamin Rosenzweig, 1995-07-10, AFC 2003/002: MV118; Tape 5 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Benjamin Rosenzweig, 1995-07-10, AFC 2003/002: MV119; Tape 6 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with: Benjamin Rosenzweig, 1995-07-10, AFC 2003/002: MV120; Tape 7 of 7, Betacam SP
  - Luboml Douglas/Steiman Productions, 2001-08-21, AFC 2003/002: MV121; Tape 1, Betacam SP
  - Luboml Douglas/Steiman Productions, 2001-08-21, AFC 2003/002: MV122; Tape 2, Betacam SP
  - Luboml Douglas/Steiman Productions, 2001-08-21, AFC 2003/002: MV123; Tape 3, Betacam SP
  - Luboml Douglas/Steiman Productions, 2001-08-21, AFC 2003/002: MV124; Tape 4, Betacam SP
  - Luboml Douglas/Steiman Productions, 2001-08-21, AFC 2003/002: MV125; Tape 5, Betacam SP
  - Luboml Douglas/Steiman Productions, 2001-08-21, AFC 2003/002: MV126; Tape 6, Betacam SP
  - Luboml Douglas/Steiman Productions, 2001-08-21, AFC 2003/002: MV127; Tape 7, Betacam SP
  - Luboml Douglas/Steiman Productions, 2001-08-21, AFC 2003/002: MV128; Tape 8, Betacam SP
  - Luboml Douglas/Steiman Productions, 2001-11-14, AFC 2003/002: MV129; Tape 9, Betacam SP
  - Luboml Douglas/Steiman Productions, and Luboml Reshoots, 01-11-14/2002-02-14, AFC 2003/002: MV130; Tape 10, Betacam SP
  - Digitizing Re shoots, 2002-02-22, AFC 2003/002: MV131; Betacam SP
  - Luboml - Ukraine, 2001-07-14, AFC 2003/002: MV132; Tape 1, Betacam SP
  - Luboml, 2001-07-14, AFC 2003/002: MV133; Tape 2, Betacam SP
  - Luboml, AFC 2003/002: MV134; Tape 3, Betacam SP
  - Luboml, AFC 2003/002: MV135; Tape 4, Betacam SP
  - Luboml, AFC 2003/002: MV136; Tape 5, Betacam SP
  - Luboml, AFC 2003/002: MV137; Tape 6, Betacam SP
  - Luboml, AFC 2003/002: MV138; Tape 7, Betacam SP
  - Luboml, AFC 2003/002: MV139; Tape 8, Betacam SP
  - Luboml, AFC 2003/002: MV140; Tape 9, Betacam SP
  - Luboml, AFC 2003/002: MV141; Tape 10, Betacam SP
  - Interview with Nat Sobel, 2001-07-31, AFC 2003/002: MV142; Tape 5, Betacam SP
  - Interview with Nat Sobel, 2001-07-31, AFC 2003/002: MV143; Tape 6, Betacam SP
  - Nat Sobel: Songs and still shots, 2001-07-31, AFC 2003/002: MV144; Tape 7, Betacam SP
  - Interview with Aaron Ziegelman, 2001-07-31, AFC 2003/002: MV145; Tape 1, Betacam SP
  - Interview with Aaron Ziegelman, 2001-07-31, AFC 2003/002: MV146; Tape 2, Betacam SP
  - Interview with Abe Getman, 2001-07-31, AFC 2003/002: MV147; Tape 3, Betacam SP
  - Interview with Abe Getman, 2001-07-31, AFC 2003/002: MV148; Tape 4, Betacam SP
  - Sonia Orbuch Selects, AFC 2003/002: MV149; Betacam, SP
  - Luboml Douglas/Steiman Productions, 2001-08-21, AFC 2003/002: MV150; Tape 1 and 2, VHS
  - Luboml Douglas/Steiman Productions, 2001-08-21, AFC 2003/002: MV151; Tape 3 and 4, VHS
  - Luboml Douglas/Steiman Productions, 2001-08-21, AFC 2003/002: MV152; Tape 5 and 6, VHS
  - Luboml Douglas/Steiman Productions, 2001-08-21, AFC 2003/002: MV153; Tapes 7 and 8, VHS
  - Luboml Douglas/Steiman Productions, 2001-11-14, AFC 2003/002: MV154; Tapes 9 and 10, VHS
  - Lillian Chaneles, 1995-07-25, AFC 2003/002: MV155; Tape 1-3, VHS
  - Nathan Eiger, 1995-07-17, AFC 2003/002: MV156; Tape 1-4 of 6, VHS
  - Nathan Eiger, 1995-07-17, AFC 2003/002: MV157; Tape 5-6 of 6, VHS
  - Ann Gershengorn, AFC 2003/002: MV158; Tape 1-3, VHS
  - Ann Friedman Gershengorn, AFC 2003/002: MV159; Tape 1-3, VHS
  - Victor Gershengorn, 1995-06-19, AFC 2003/002: MV160; Tape 1 of 2, VHS
  - Victor Gershengorn, 1995-06-19, AFC 2003/002: MV161; Tape 2 of 2, VHS
  - Victor Gershengorn, AFC 2003/002: MV162; Tape 1-3, VHS
  - Victor Gershengorn, AFC 2003/002: MV163; Tape 1-3, VHS
  - Victor Gershengorn, AFC 2003/002: MV164; Tape 4-5, VHS
  - Victor Gershengorn, AFC 2003/002: MV165; Tape 4-5, VHS
  - Victor Gershengorn, AFC 2003/002: MV166; Tape 4-5, VHS
  - Victor Gershengorn, 1995, AFC 2003/002: MV167; Tape 1 of 2, VHS
  - Victor Gershengorn Interview, 1995, AFC 2003/002: MV168; Tape 2 of 2, VHS
  - Abe Getman, AFC 2003/002: MV169; Tape 1 of 2, VHS
  - Abe Getman, AFC 2003/002: MV170; Tape 2 of 2, VHS
  - Abe Getman, AFC 2003/002: MV171; Tape 1 of 2, VHS
  - Abe Getman, AFC 2003/002: MV172; Tape 2 of 2, VHS
  - Abe Getman #1 2001-07-31, AFC 2003/002: MV173; Tape 1 of 2, VHS
  - Abe Getman #2, 2001-07-31, AFC 2003/002: MV174; Tape 2 of 2, VHS
  - May Shuster Goodman, 1995-08-31, AFC 2003/002: MV175; Tape 1-4, VHS
  - May Shuster Goodman, 1995-08-13, AFC 2003/002: MV176; Tape 5, VHS
  - Esther Ziegelman Kessler Interview, 1995-05-24, AFC 2003/002: MV177; Tape 1 of 2, VHS
  - Esther Ziegelman Kessler Interview, 1995-05-24, AFC 2003/002: MV178; Tape 2 of 2, VHS
  - Esther Kessler Interview, 1995-05-24, AFC 2003/002: MV179; Tape 1
  - Esther Kessler Interview, 1995-05-24, AFC 2003/002: MV180; VHS
  - Esther Kessler Interview, 1995-05-24, AFC 2003/002: MV181; VHS
  - Esther Kessler Interview, 1995-05-24, AFC 2003/002: MV182; VHS
  - Victor Lichtmacher, AFC 2003/002: MV183; VHS
  - Victor Gershengorn, AFC 2003/002: MV184; VHS
  - Victor Lichtmacher, AFC 2003/002: MV185; VHS
  - Victor Lichtmacher, AFC 2003/002: MV186; VHS
  - Bernard Meller, 1995-09-21, AFC 2003/002: MV187; VHS
  - Bernard Meller, 1995-09-21, AFC 2003/002: MV188; VHS
  - Clara Pozner Interview, AFC 2003/002: MV189; VHS
  - Clara Pozner Interview, AFC 2003/002: MV190; VHS
  - Esther Pachter, 1995-08-15, AFC 2003/002: MV191; VHS
  - Esther Pachter, 1995-08-15, AFC 2003/002: MV192; VHS
  - Esther Pachter, 1995-08-15, AFC 2003/002: MV193; VHS
  - Riwa Plotnik, 1996-08-01, AFC 2003/002: MV194; VHS
  - Riwa Plotnik, 1996-08-01, AFC 2003/002: MV195; VHS
  - Moshe Shalev, 1995-06-30, AFC 2003/002: MV196; VHS
  - Moshe Shalev, 1995-06-30, AFC 2003/002: MV197; VHS
  - Moshe Shalev, AFC 2003/002: MV198; VHS
  - Benjamin Rosenzweig, AFC 2003/002: MV199; VHS
  - Benjamin Rosenzweig, AFC 2003/002: MV200; VHS
  - Benjamin Rosenzweig, AFC 2003/002: MV201; VHS
  - Benjamin Rosenzweig, AFC 2003/002: MV202; VHS
  - Moshe Shalev, AFC 2003/002: MV203; VHS
  - Moshe Shalev, AFC 2003/002: MV204; VHS
  - Moshe Shalev, AFC 2003/002: MV205; VHS
  - Nathan Sobel, AFC 2003/002: MV206; VHS
  - Nathan Sobel, AFC 2003/002: MV207; VHS
  - Nathan Sobel, AFC 2003/002: MV208; VHS
  - Nathan Sobel, AFC 2003/002: MV209; VHS
  - Nathan Sobel, AFC 2003/002: MV210; VHS
  - Nathan Sobel, AFC 2003/002: MV211; VHS
  - Aaron Ziegelman, 2001-07-31, AFC 2003/002: MV212; VHS
  - Aaron Ziegelman, 2001-07-31, AFC 2003/002: MV213; VHS
  - Aaron Ziegelman, AFC 2003/002: MV214; VHS
  - Aaron Ziegelman, AFC 2003/002: MV215; VHS
  - Nathan Sobel, 2001-07-31, AFC 2003/002: MV216; VHS
  - Nathan Sobel, 2001-07-31, AFC 2003/002: MV217; VHS
  - Nathan Sobel, 2001-07-31, AFC 2003/002: MV218; VHS
  - Aaron Ziegelman, AFC 2003/002: MV219; VHS
  - Aaron Ziegelman, AFC 2003/002: MV220; VHS
  - Reel 1 Ukraine, AFC 2003/002: MV221; VHS
    Aaron Ziegelman and Abe at the Memorial Day walking on the Killing Field.
  - Reel 2 Ukraine, AFC 2003/002: MV222; VHS
    Fields, Aaron Ziegelman and Abe in town market, Jagiello.
  - Luboml Reel 3, AFC 2003/002: MV223; VHS
    School, old houses and streets, train station and tracks, evening fields.
  - Luboml Reel 4, AFC 2003/002: MV224; VHS
    Memorial night
  - Luboml #5, AFC 2003/002: MV225; VHS
    Cows, museum, streets houses and wagon.
  - Luboml # 6, AFC 2003/002: MV226; VHS
    Olga's house, Anna's house night shot, window in the house, cows.
  - Luboml #7, AFC 2003/002: MV227; VHS
    Church high shot, tower high shot of town, Mikola's house-photos, kerosene, lamp, oven, outhouse, horses and wagons, tree in cemetery.
  - Luboml Reel #8, AFC 2003/002: MV228; VHS
    Bug River, fields, traveling shots, Olivne, on bench Abe and Aaron Ziegelman.
  - Luboml #9, AFC 2003/002: MV229; VHS
    Olivne continued, Abe and Aaron Ziegelman on bench continued, moon, sunrise, Luboml in town contempt.
  - Luboml #10, AFC 2003/002: MV230; VHS
    final shots, more train, men in fields and sky.
  - Luboml at Yad Vershem Summer 1997, AFC 2003/002: MV231; Tape 1 of 2, VHS
  - Luboml – At Yad Vershem, Summer 1997, AFC 2003/002: MV232; Tape 2 of 2, VHS
  - Meller Tape of 1991 Luboml Trip, 1991, AFC 2003/002: MV233; VHS
  - Miriam Weiner and Vitaly Chumak’s Visit to Luboml, 1995-08, AFC 2003/002: MV234; Tape 1, VHS
  - Luboml Exhibition Project Delegation, 1995-09, AFC 2003/002: MV235; Tape 1, VHS
    Video fragments-Ukrainian TV coverage of Luboml Exhibition Project Delegation, arrival in Luboml.
  - LEP Trip to Luboml, 1995-09, AFC 2003/002: MV236; VHS
    NTSC dub video fragments; Ukrainian TV coverage of Luboml Exhibition Project delegation arrival in Luboml.
  - Abe Getman’s visit to Luboml, 1995-09, AFC 2003/002: MV237; VHS
  - A. Ziegelman – Luboml and Ustilug, AFC 2003/002: MV238; Tape 2, VHS
  - Cymerbojm, AFC 2003/002: MV239; VHS
  - Cymerbojm, AFC 2003/002: MV240; VHS
  - Edward Dunitz: Holocaust Oral History, AFC 2003/002: MV241; 1 hour 24 mins, VHS
  - Aaron Eiger Interviewing Shlomo Eiger, AFC 2003/002: MV242; VHS
  - Karpus Interview 1-4, AFC 2003/002: MV243; VHS
  - Karpus Interview 5-8, AFC 2003/002: MV244; VHS
  - Karpus, AFC 2003/002: MV245; VHS
  - Karpus, AFC 2003/002: MV246; VHS
  - Victor Gershengorn, AFC 2003/002: MV247; VHS
  - Cymerbojm 3, 1995-09, AFC 2003/002: MV248; Tape 10, VHS
    Dub of Luboml interview.
  - Cymerbojm 2, 1995-09, AFC 2003/002: MV249; Tape 11, VHS
  - Cymerbojm 1, 1995-09, AFC 2003/002: MV250; Tape 13, VHS
  - Miriam Weiner and Vitalychumak’s Visit to Luboml, 1995-08, AFC 2003/002: MV251; Tape 2, VHS
  - This is What I Remember About Libivne, 1996-03-07, AFC 2003/002: MV252; 18 minutes, VHS
    Excerpts from oral history interviews with former residents of Luboml (Libivne) West End, Synagogue copy.
  - This is What I Remember Of Libivne, 1996-03-22, AFC 2003/002: MV253; Betacam
  - This is What I Remember Of Libivne, 1997-02, AFC 2003/002: MV254; 15 minutes, VHS
  - This is what I remember of Libivne, 1996-03-09, AFC 2003/002: MV255; VHS
  - This is what I remember of Libivne, AFC 2003/002: MV256; VHS
  - “Luboml, 1933” “This is What I Remember About Libivne...”, 1996, AFC 2003/002: MV257; 30 minutes, VHS
  - The Children of Chabannes, AFC 2003/002: MV258; 53 minutes, VHS
  - Eye On the World: Together At Last, 1994-02-22, AFC 2003/002: MV259; 83 minutes, VHS
  - Together At Last, AFC 2003/002: MV260; 83 minutes, VHS
  - Together At Last, 2004-06-10, AFC 2003/002: MV261; 53 minutes, VHS
    Ziegelman Family Reunion speaks about Luboml before the family left for America, narrative of shootings; not in concentration camps, cuts from Ethel Zimmerman home mover, 1933. About 35 family members (Brazil, North America and South America are interviewed) 1 duplicate copy exists.
  - Luboml: My Heart Remembers, >, AFC 2003/002: MV262; 67:16, VHS
  - Luboml: My Heart Remembers, 2002-10-07, AFC 2003/002: MV263; 56:30, Betacam SP Mega
  - Memo 38: Computeranimation der ehemaligen Synagoge am Michelsberg, AFC 2003/002: MV264; VHS
    Visualisieerung der ehemaligen Wiesbadener Synagogue am Michelsberg (visualization of the former Wiesbadener synagogue).
  - Kein Tag wie jeder andere (Not a day like any other), 1993, AFC 2003/002: MV265; 34 minutes, VHS
  - Talkline with Zev Brenner, 1997-11-03, AFC 2003/002: MV266; 42 minutes, VHS
    Exhibit opening at Yeshiva University. 2 duplicate copies exists.
  - Luboml Program: Cardozo Opening, 1997-09-09, AFC 2003/002: MV267; VHS
  - VHS cassette, AFC 2003/002: MV268; VHS
  - VHS cassette, AFC 2003/002: MV269; VHS
  - Remembering Luboml, 1999-03-08, AFC 2003/002: MV270; VHS
  - Remembering Luboml, 1999-03-07, AFC 2003/002: MV271; VHS
  - Aaron Svah, 1999-03-07, AFC 2003/002: MV272; VHS
  - “Luboml 1933” combo: This is What I Remember, AFC 2003/002: MV273; Betacam Mega
  - Luboml Loop Master, 1999-11-01, AFC 2003/002: MV274; Betacam Mega
  - Poland Footage: Ethel Zim footage Luboml, 1933, AFC 2003/002: MV275; 14 minutes, Betacam
  - Luboml – Ethel Zim Footage, AFC 2003/002: MV276_original; 1 film reel (8 mm)
    See folder 40/638 for documentation.
  - Luboml – Ethel Zim Footage, AFC 2003/002: MV276; VHS
  - Ethel Zim Footage, AFC 2003/002: MV277; VHS
  - Ukraine Trip #1, 1995-09, AFC 2003/002: MV278; Tape 1, VHS
  - Ukraine Trip #1, 1995-09, AFC 2003/002: MV279; Tapes 3, 5 and 6, VHS
    Old lady, her village, old women house and garden.
  - Ukraine Trip #2, 1995-09, AFC 2003/002: MV280; Tapes 2-5, VHS
    Old house; inside local house.
  - Ukraine Trip #3, 1995-09, AFC 2003/002: MV281; Tapes 6-9, VHS
    House-exterior make black and white, slow down Also Sobel’s house.
  - Ukraine Trip #4, 1995-09, AFC 2003/002: MV282; Tapes 10-12, VHS
    White haired lady, Luboml today-Slovakia Lenin Street Tram Station
  - Ukraine #5, 1995-09, AFC 2003/002: MV283; Tape 13, VHS
  - #7, AFC 2003/002: MV284; VHSC Maxell
  - Kotler #2, AFC 2003/002: MV285; Tape 2 of 2, VHSC Maxell
  - #12, AFC 2003/002: MV286; VHSC Maxell
  - Aleksandr Sologub, AFC 2003/002: MV287; VHSC Maxell
  - Kotler #1, AFC 2003/002: MV288; Tape 1 of 2, VHSC Maxell
  - 1. Lvov, AFC 2003/002: MV289; Tape 1, Maxell
  - Holovno, AFC 2003/002: MV290; VHSC Maxell